# KRITIK SAH

## WEB DEVELOPER



- +91 7021245436
- kritiksahco@gmail.com
- Mumbai / Bangalore, India
- in <u>linkedin.com/in/kritiksah/</u>
- cryptolancer.in Portfolio
- youtube.com/itrebels
- English, Hindi & Marathi
- linktr.ee/kritik

## SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- NodeJS/javascript knowledge
- React, Redux, Next. js experience
- Mongodb, postman
- On page SEO
- · Good understanding of web3 tech
- Solidity, Ethers.js, Wagmi, foundry EVM chains.
- Git/Github & version control
- PM Tools (Jira for scrum/agile)
- Good Communication
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind css
   , SCSS experience
- CMS like Wordpress.

## PROFILE

Greetings! I'm Kritik Sah, a front-end developer with 3+ years experience. My journey includes frontend leadership at a web3 firm, contributions to a marketing agency and online pharmacy e-com projects, and a strong passion for user-centric UI and open-source.

# EXPERIENCE

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER (REACT, NEXTJS, WEB3)

Omega Athena Technology Private Ltd / DAOstruct

### Mar 2023 - Present

 I enhanced my React and Next.js skills while spearheading the front-end development for an early-stage startup's MVP, concurrently improving on-page SEO, delving into the Web3 ecosystem, attending relevant events, and honing project management abilities as a founding front-end developer.

## SDE I - FRONTEND (REACTJS, REDUX)

Intellihealth Solutions Pvt. Ltd. / Truemeds

## Nov 2022 - Mar 2023

 I worked with Truemeds, a digital pharmacy and consultancy startup, on various admin and management portals, enhancing my React.js skills in the process.

#### JR. FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Tonic WorldWide pvt. Ltd.

### Aug 2021 - Oct 2022

In my first IT job as a self-taught developer, I gained confidence
and knowledge, working on numerous web projects, creating over
100+ mailers in six months, improving various skills including
blogging, phpMyAdmin, Photoshop, and cleaning PHP and MySQL
backend code (though I'm still learning in this area), with a primary
focus on frontend technologies like HTML, CSS, Bootstrap,
jQuery, and JavaScript.

## EDUCATION

# BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (MATHEMATICS)

Mumbai University

2018 - 2021

#### HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL

Maharashtra Board

2016 - 2018

## AWARDS

- Polygon Road to Web3 Hackathon
   Winner Badge.
- Polygon Road to Web3 Hackathon
   Participant Badge
- Web3 Twitter Buidler moralis

## **PROJECTS**

- Portfolio
- ServicesStrategy.com
- infinitelearning.org.in
- Fitndur
- Cocktail recipe application
- NASA PID Next 13 application
- Bank Dapp with smart contract
- NFT Gating website(Dapp)

# LEARNING

- Smart contract development & testing
- · Professional video editing
- Videography
- · Community building
- How to enjoy my life ;p

## CERTIFICATIONS

## FREECODECAMP.ORG CERTIFICATIONS:

- <u>Responsive Web Design</u>: All about HTML, CSS, and the foundation of web development.
- <u>JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures</u>: Foundation of javascript with Data structure and Algorithms.
- <u>Front End Development Libraries</u>: In the Front End Development Libraries Certification, I learned how to style our site quickly with Bootstrap & how to create powerful Single Page Applications (SPAs) with React and Redux.
- Data Visualization: Data Visualization with D3.

### **UDEMY COURSE CERTIFICATIONS:**

- The Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp Dr. Angela Yu
- Linux for Absolute Beginners!
- Linux BASH Shell Terminal Command Basics
- Python: Master Programming and Development with 15 Projects

#### **ALCHEMY UNIVERSITY CERTIFICATIONS:**

JavaScript Fundamentals

#### METACRAFTERS ACADEMY CERTIFICATIONS:

- ETH PROOF: Beginner EVM Course
- ETH PROOF: Intermediate EVM Course

# OPEN SOURCE



## 2023 POAP.GALLERY CONTRIBUTOR

open source contribution in poap.gallery website to fix a bug, that was causing blank page website error (crash)



## 2023 ETHEREUM.ORG CONTRIBUTOR

open source contribution in ethereum.org AKA Ethereum Foundation website to fix bugs in their documentation and other multiple changes.

# **WORKING ON**

- IT Rebels DAO (Onboard 1000 devs in web3) currently 7.1k subs
- 13+ dapp projects for teaching purpose
- Myself so i can be a better human being.